Guide to the Office of Institutional Research, Yale University, Records and Reports
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Research reports and correspondence, 1955-1984; Accession 1987-A-019
  - Research Reports and Materials
    - Study of Transfer Students Classes of 1958-1962; RP 337 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Transfer Study - List of Transfers; RP 337, 1961 May (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Transfer Study - Interviewed by BH; RP 337, 1961 May (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Transfer Study - 1964 Material Gathered (and then Study was Canceled); RP 337 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Re-admission Case Study; RP 338, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Freshman Curriculum - Satisfactions with Survey for the Present Committee; RP 341 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Curriculum Study for Yale College Committee/Honors Study Enrollment; RP 345, 345A, 1962 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Geology Department Study (GRE Study) Students entering in 1962 Mar 2; RP 400 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Psychology Department Studies; RP 402 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Undergraduate Enrollment in Chemistry (Prof. Harry Wasserman); RP 403 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Electrical Engineering; Engineering and Applied Science (Prof. Clarke); RP 404 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Predicting Freshman Year Records of Naval Science Students, 1965-67 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Yale University Graduate School Study of Students Admitted; RP 407, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Data on Yale Graduate School Matriculants; RP 407, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 24 - 25)
    - Date from the Study of Yale Graduate School Enrollees; RP 407, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Xerox copies, Tables 7-20 and originals; RP 407 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Alumni Survey - Graduate School; RP 408, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Yale Graduate School - Control Records; RP 408 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Statistical Summary of Yale Graduate School Degree Recipients 1900-1967; RP 408, 1969 March 25 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Statistical Summary of Yale Graduate School Degree Recipients 1900-1967; RP 408, 1969 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Yale Graduate School Ph.D Recipients classified by Employment, by Division, and by Department; RP 408, 1969 April 10 (Box 2, Folder 32 - 33)
    - Yale Graduate School Alumni Survey - Summary of Data; RP 408, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Yale Graduate School Alumni Survey - Summaries; RP 408, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Statistical Summary - control copy (Paul S. Burnham); RP 408 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Division II Study - Questionnaires; RP 409, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Divisional and Intensive Majors Dean May - Prof. Lindblum; RP 409, 1967 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Survey of Reactions to Divisional Majors in Yale College; RP 409, 1967 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - History Department Study - Class of 1968 (Prof. Turner); RP 411, 1967 June (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Biology Study forr Prof. Stowe; RP 412 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Nursing School Study; RP 413, 1958-1968 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Origins, Performance, Plans - Class of 1959-1961; RP 460 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Class of 1965; RP 465 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Change i n Choice of Major for Science and Engineering Groups - Class of 1965; RP 465, 1967 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Shifts in Science Majors; RP 465C, 1967 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Preliminary Report on Post-Graduate Plans - Seniors, Class of 1966; RP 466, 1966 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 1974-1975; RP 470-473 (Box 2)
    - Class Enrollments, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 48 - 50)
    - Class Enrollments, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 51 - 52)
  - Correspondence
    - 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence of John Goldin (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Records, 1975-1985; Accession 1987-A-070
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Past Employees, circa 1977-1985
  - Yale Printing Service
    - 1911-18 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Publications, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18 - 19)
  - Purchase Orders, Invoices, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20 - 21)
  - Travel, Expense Reports, 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 22 - 24)
  - Questionnaires
    - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 26)
    - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27 - 28)
    - 1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Reports on student academic performance, 1974-1975; Accession 1987-A-083
  - Dimensions of Student Performance in Yale College - a first report of the College Criteria Study, 1974 November 15 (Box 1)
  - Patterns of a Successful Performance in Yale College - a second report of the College Criteria Study, 1975 August 28 (Box 1)
- Records, 1968-1986; Accession 1988-A-100
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
  - College Criteria Study:
    - Prestudy Interview Summaries, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
    - Prestudy Working Papers
      - No. 1, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - No. 2, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - No. 3, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - No. 4, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - No. 5, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - No. 6, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Proposal for Further Study, 1972 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Questionnaire, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Prestudy Report
      - No. 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - No. 2, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - No. 3, 1973 July 12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - No. 4, 1973 July 12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Interim Report, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - (First Report): "Dimensions of Student Performance in Yale College", 1974 November15 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - (Second Report): Working Draft, 1975 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - (Second Report): "Patterns of Successful Performance in Yale College", 1975 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - (Second Report Addendum): Relationship of Success Types to Quantified Admissions Variables", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - (Third Report): "Patterns of Unsuccessful Performance in Yale College", 1975 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - (Third Report Addendum): Relationship of Unsuccessful Types to Quantified Admissions Variables'', 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Report on Multiple Nominees, 1974 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - The Seven Types of Student Success", undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Typologies of Student Success, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - The Multiple Dimensions ofCollege Success, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - A Profile of the Multiple Evaluating Environments Within a College, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - The Yale College Experience andPost-College Planning, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Memos on College Criteria Study, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - English Essay Study 1975-1976:
    - Admissions Data - Class of 1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence with Other Colleges (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Department of English Data (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Instructions and Methods (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Letter Lists (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Memos and Notes (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Preliminary Results (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Yale College Freshmen - How Well do They Write? - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Computer Data (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - English Essay Study
    - 1979-1980: Recording Sheets (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - 1983-1984: Computer Data (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 1983-1984: Essays and Memos (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 1983-1984: Student Information (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Research - English Department, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Computers in Writing Study, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Seven-College Writing Conference: Memos and Information, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Seven-College Writing Conference: Drafts and Proposals, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Senior Profile Study 1979-1980:
    - General (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Administration (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Advisory Meetings Report (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Data Preparation and Analysis (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Dimensions (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Interview Administration (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Interviewers (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Interviewer Training (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Other Responses (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Participant Comment (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Types (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Variables and Codes (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Verbal Descriptions (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous Notes and Memos (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Senior Studies, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Senior Study:
    - 1978 - Computer Data (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - 1978 - Class of 1978 List of Graduates (Box 5, Folder 65 - 66)
    - 1979 - Notes and Memos (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - 1979 - Correspondence and Memos (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - 1979 - Degree Lists (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - 1979 - Student List (Box 5, Folder 70 - 72)
  - Admissions reports, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Yale College Study Group (YCSG) Survey:
    - Reviews of Books on Higher Educations, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Questionnaires, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Preliminary Results, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Factbook on Yale University, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 77 - 78)
  - Factbook on Yale University, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Testing Controversy, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - HEGIS (Higher Education General Information Survey):
    - 1977-1978: General Information (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Graduate Degrees Conferred, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Bachelor Degrees Conferred, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Professional Degrees Conferred, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Graduate School Degrees, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Graduate School Degrees, 1978 May-December (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - 1978-1979: Memos and Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - 1978-1979: Degree Lists (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - 1979-1980: Memos and Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - 1979-1980: Student Lists (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - 1980-1981: Data and Forms (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - 1981-1982: Data and Forms (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - 1981-1982: Student Lists (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - 1982-1983: General Information (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Questionnaires (from other Institutions), 1982 August - October (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Questionnaires:
    - 1982 Nov - Dec (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - 1983 Jan - Feb (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - 1983 Mar - Jun (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - 1983 Jul - Nov (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - 1984 Jan - Mar (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - 1984 Mar - Jul (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - 1984 Jun - Dec (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - 1985 Jan - Mar (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - 1985 Apr - Jun (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Summaries of Office of Institutional Research Reports, 1968-1978 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Notes for an Evaluation of the Office of Institutional Research 1971-1975, 1975 March 10 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Budget and Personnel
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - COMPUTER PRINTOUTS (Box 10)
    - English Essay Study, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - BEGIS: Degrees Conferred, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Senior Class Surveys, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Personnel - Salaries and Wages, 1979-1985 (Box 11, Folder 116)
- Factfile #1, 1986; Accession 1989-A-065
  - OIR 86R020; Factfile #1 -statistics about students, student aid and faculty, 1986 August (Box 1)
- "College and Afterlife" study, circa 1944; Accession 1989-A-089
  - "College and Afterlife" (study), circa 1944 (Box 1)
- Grade distribution reports, 1933-1967; Accession 1989-A-092
  - Grade distribution reports
    - 1933-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Records, 1962-1990; Accession 1991-A-036
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - A Yale Scientific Magazine Article: Undergraduate Enrollment in the Sciences: A problem or a Non-Problem? (RP 465), 1965 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Changes in Choice of Major for Science and Engineering Groups in the Class of 1965 (RP 465) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1965: Study of Changes in Major in Science and Engineering Groups (RP 465) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Coeducation 1969-1970 (Report Prepared by Elga Wasserman), 1970 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ConnecticutBoard of Higher Education: Planning and Leisure (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, General, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, General, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Enrollment of Connecticut Students: Connecticut Public Law 73-551 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Health and Education Facilities Authority, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Language Statistics (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Language Study for Yale College, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Questionnaires
    - Completed, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12 - 14)
    - Forwarded to Other Offices, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Dead, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Completed, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17 - 22)
    - Forwarded to Other Offices, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Dead, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Scholastic Aptitude Tests (SAT's) in Yale College (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Shifts in Science Interests (RP 465), 1962 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Title IX Report, 1974 Fall (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - YaleCollegeProposals for Degree Programs, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - University-wide: Cumulative Debt Student Data and Analysis
    - Class of 1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Class of 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30 - 31)
  - Admissions Statistics Binder (Box 1, Folder 32 - 34)
  - University Fact book, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 35, Box 2, Folder 36-39)
- Yale University Fact Book, 1992-1993; Accession 1993-A-076
  - Yale University Fact Book, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
- Financial aid, student loan and Peabody Museum records, 1971-1991; Accession 1995-A-076
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026
  - Financial Aid Policies (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General Outlines, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Schools of Medicine, Nursing, and EPH, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Schools of Forestry and Divinity, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Schools of Management, Law, Music, and Sacred Music, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Schools of Art and Architecture and Drama, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Financial Aid at Yale (draft), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Other Materials
    - Surveys, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Budget Analysis
    - Budget vs Actual University Wide Income, 1971-1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Term Bill Income and Student Expenditures, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Budget vs Actual Tuition Income
      - 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1981 -1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Analyses
    - Loan Default Analysis
      - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Application Transfer Team, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Peabody Museum Visitors Survey, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Data, analyses, and research files, 1970-1997; Accession 2001-A-028
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  - Yale College Admissions Data
    - Class of 1974 (Box 1)
    - Class of 1975
    - Class of 1976
    - Class of 1977
    - Class of 1978
    - Class of 1980 (3 notebooks) (Box 2)
  - YaleCollegeMinority Analysis - Class of 1977
  - Yale College Admissions Data
    - Classes of 1981 and 1982 (Box 3)
    - Class of 1983
    - Class of 1984
  - Yale College Financial Aid Data
    - Classes of 1975-1977 (Box 4)
    - Classes of 1977-1980
    - Classes of 1979-1981 (Box 5)
  - YaleCollegeMinority Analysis - Class of 1976
  - YaleCollegePre-med Analysis -Classes of 1978-1979
  - YaleCollegeFinancial Aid Data - Classes of 1982-1984 (2 notebooks) (Box 6)
  - Faculty and Staff Manfile Counts
    - 1992 (Box 7)
    - 1992
    - 1991
    - 1991
    - 1990
    - 1990
    - 1989
    - 1986
    - 1973 to 1981
    - 1992 (Box 8)
    - 1993
    - 1993 to 1994
    - 1994
    - 1995
    - 1995
    - 1996
    - 1996
    - 1997
  - Computer Usage -- Survey of Students (2 folders), 1986 (Box 9)
  - Staff Analyses and Adjustments, Staff Salaries, 1984-1985
  - Staff and Managerial and Professional Analyses
  - ST 1.0 December 1 Adjustments -, 1982
  - ST 2.0 Manfile Focus Stuff
  - ST 3.0 Raises, Staff, 1983 July 1
  - ST 4.0 Staff Position Control Committee
  - ST 5 MandP Salary Analysis, 1985
  - Priorities and Planning (Szczarba)
  - Science Hill Task Force
  - Final Report
  - Phase II, 1995-1996
  - Task Force II (Back-up Reports for data - early versions)
  - FY 95 GandC Expenses, 1994-1995
  - CPP Project, 1970/71 - 1979/80, Fall 1980
  - Women's Table Files (created after 1970) (Box 10)
  - Tally Sheets (for Sculpture) Graduate School
  - All Women 1906 and Earlier and 1943-1970
  - Total Enrollment 1943-1951
  - Total Enrollment 1951-1954
  - Total Enrollment 1964-1976
- Yale College Class of 2006: A Study of Activities One Year After Graduation, 2007; Accession 2008-A-073
  - Yale College Class of 2006: A Study of Activities One Year After Graduation, 2007 (Box 1)
- Records, 1969-2014; Accession 2017-A-014
  Restricted until January 1, 2090.
  - University financial aid and student loans-historical statistics, 1969-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University-wide debt background study and report, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cumulative debt summaries-includes raw data, analyses and surveys
    - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
    - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Yale College debt analysis by race and sex, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University financial aid /loans: other, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Financial aid studies for Yale schools-includes summary statistics
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2a)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Starting salaries data-includes professional schools
    - 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Yale College review of Senior projects, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 18-20)
  - Course of Study Committee work on Senior projects
    - General, 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Course of study: Chairs questions about the major, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - DUS survey of senior requirements, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Alumni comments, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Student alums survey about senior requirements, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - International Alliance of Research Universities (IARU)
  - Administration, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Institution surveys, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Report on women, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Yale College post-graduation studies
    - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 2002-2008 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Yale Univesrity statistical profile: "A Statistical Overview of Yale University and New Haven", 2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Yale Book of Numbers, 1976-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Ongoing Book of Numbers, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - University-wide grants and contracts-department monitoring, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Grants and Contracts by faculty PI surveys -completed and summaries
    - 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 6-9)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Grants and Contracts summaries, 1984-1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Graduate School course registration statistics
    - 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Graudate School almuni survey data, 1900-1967 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Graudate School-students declining admissions, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Departmental statistics
    - 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Association of Yale Alumni-"Admissions to Yale and the Financing of a Yale University Education", 1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Admissions data: "Old Bogey Procedure Material", 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Report: "Athletes and Non-Athletes at Highly Selective Schools", 2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - GESO report on Yale investments, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Yale University workplace study, 2005-2008 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Yale College grade reports, 1963-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Senior studies: Activities one-year following graduation, 1967-1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Yale College registration trends, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "Gallimore Study": Yale College migration of undergraduates in the sciences, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Matriculation yields by Yale College admissions major, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Yale College undergraduate instruction project, 1983-1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)